

LORENZO RIGATO

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

A dedicated 26 years old full-stack developer with 5+ years of experience in web and mobile apps development.

Strong knowledge on Ruby on Rails and Android technologies.

Passionate on data engineering.

Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfying customer's requirements.

Clean code lover and beautiful UI fascinated.

CONTACT



lore91tanz@gmail.com

+39 333 8600532

Viale Brigata Marche, 33 Treviso, 31100

PERSONAL SKILLS

MOTIVATION

QUICK LEARNER

TEAMWORK

PROBLEM SOLVING



WORK EXPERIENCE

ANDROID & IOS DEVELOPER

Previnet SPA – Treviso, Italy

Nov 2016 to Current

Development of an application for a bank on both Android & iOS platforms about managing health services.

WEB DEVELOPER

REPLY SPA — Milan, Italy
Apr 2016 to Oct 2016

Development of responsive websites in Liferay.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

BELKA SRL - Trento, Italy
Jan 2016 to Mar 2016

Development of two Android applications. First about sharing events between friends. Second on chips configuration via NFC.

FULL-STACK AND MOBILE DEVELOPER

FONDAZIONE BRUNO KESSLER – Trento, Italy
Dec 2011 to Dec 2015

- Design and development of Ruby on Rails and Android applications against food waste.
- Aggregation and organization from different sources of food information.
- Worked closely with senior developers. Learned advanced programming and project management skills.



EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE MASTER DEGREE

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO
110 CUM LAUDE / 110
December 2015

COMPUTER SCIENCE BACHELOR DEGREE

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO
103 / 110
September 2013

ECONOMY HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

ICT RICCATI OF TREVISO
81 / 100
June 2010



iOS

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

ANDROID	USER INTERACTION & UX
RUBY ON RAILS	ANGULAR JS

ADOBE CS6